pocketly.com 2016-11-23

# Privacy Policy

Here at Pocketly we recognize that your privacy is very important, and to keep you informed about our privacy practices we ask that you please read the guidelines described below. Keep in mind that because Pocketly is growing and internet technologies are constantly evolving, these guidelines are subject to change and any said changes will be posted on this page. Pocketly is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of websites to which it may link.

### Personal Information

During registration for membership, we may collect personal information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for more information. Additionally, with your permission we may use location data via the GPS in your mobile or other device running the Pocketly App. With your permission, we also may gather information from your Facebook or Twitter profiles. We usually collect personal information directly from you although sometimes we may use agents or service providers to do this for us. When you are online, we collect information regarding the pages within our network that you visit. We may also acquire lists from other sources, both from other companies and from other public documents. For each visitor on our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

### Location Information

Use of our mobile application may, at your election, include location-based services. When you use the app, you may transmit information about your location to Pocketly. Additionally, information about your location may be collected even when you are not logged into the Pocketly application. That information will be used to offer you deals and coupons that are close to your geographic location. If you do not wish to share location information with us, you should be able to adjust the setting on your iOS mobile device to prevent our collection of Location Information by disabling the location services feature on your device.

### Use of Information

We use your information to provide our services to you, to fulfill administrative functions associated with these services, to enter into contracts with you or third parties, and for marketing and client relationship purposes. You may receive e-mails from us to let you know about new products, services, and upcoming events that may interest you. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us or you want to make changes to your e-mail settings, please change your setting under your setting tab. We will never sell or distribute your e-mail address to other companies or organizations, and your account password will always remain protected. We may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes, and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check our Privacy Policy periodically.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site or app, and they allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the cookie feature. But you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as merchandise transactions or registered services.

### Children

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) of 1998 provides safeguards to protect children who use the internet by regulating the online collection of personal information from children under the age of 13. Because of these safeguards, children under the age of 13 are not able to access or use all products and services on Pocketly.

### Use of Aggregate Data

We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our website for your computer or mobile device (e.g., the identity of your Internet browser, model of your mobile device, the type of operating system you use, your IP address, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our website and App. Pocketly may use personally identifiable information in aggregate form to improve our goods and services, including our website, and to make them more responsive to the needs of our customers. This statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by Pocketly, or provided to others as a summary report for marketing, advertising, or research purposes.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary in order to provide products or services to you. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our website.

### What else you should know about privacy on the Internet

Remember to close your browser or log out of the app when you have finished your Pocketly session. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer or mobile device with someone else or are using a computer or mobile device in a public place, like a library or internet cafe. You as an individual are responsible for the security of and access to your own computer.

Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information over the internet, this information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information in publicly accessible online forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your username and passwords and any account information.

Please be careful and responsible whenever you are using the internet.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or you would like to cancel your account, please contact us at support@Pocketly.com
